{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774866438","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774866438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 654c2da6-8621-4eea-bb1e-05f0bed34a2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774868280","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774868279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 654c2da6-8621-4eea-bb1e-05f0bed34a2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774868337","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774868337"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 654c2da6-8621-4eea-bb1e-05f0bed34a2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774876518","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774876517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 654c2da6-8621-4eea-bb1e-05f0bed34a2e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774888033","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774888033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774890268","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774890268"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" panya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PANYA"," userResponse":" PANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774891894","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774891894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" FARASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774894310","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774894310"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" START_FARASI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774898847","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774898847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" farasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FARASI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774900439","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774900439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" PUNDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774904245","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774904244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" punda"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUNDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774905856","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774905855"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" KONDOO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774910529","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774910529"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kondoo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KONDOO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774912136","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774912135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" BATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774915703","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774915703"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BATA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774917273","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774917273"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TEMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774921224","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774921224"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" tembo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TEMBO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774922802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774922802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" NYOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774926227","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774926227"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" nyoka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYOKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774927812","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774927812"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" CHURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774931190","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774931190"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774932757","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774932757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" MBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774936404","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774936403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbwa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774937959","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774937959"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" NG"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774937969","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774937969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" OMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774941194","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774941194"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NG"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774943222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774943222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ng'ombe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OMBE"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774944779","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774944779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774948580","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774948580"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" fisi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774950157","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774950157"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" PAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774953742","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774953742"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" paka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774955307","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774955307"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" MBUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774959019","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774959019"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuni"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774960577","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774960577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774964026","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774964026"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774965591","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774965591"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774969035","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774969034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" simba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774970587","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774970587"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TWIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774974207","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774974207"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" twiga"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TWIGA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774975754","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774975754"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" SONGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774979656","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774979656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" songura"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SONGURA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774981213","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774981213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" MBUZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774984803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774984803"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mbuzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774986362","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774986362"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" CHUI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774989729","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774989729"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774991739","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774991739"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774991898","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774991898"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHUI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL4.incr.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549774996688","data":{"timestamp":" 1549774996687"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:comm.wrd.animals.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775003210","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775003209"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775007436","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775007435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.12","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775014004","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775014004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775019600","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775019599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 9a0fb536-d7ed-423a-bdd2-fa376405b374"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-animals.rand.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" chui"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775039936","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775039936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tausi_tausi-nyati-dudu-mende"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tausi"," userResponse":" nyati"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775051594","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775051593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tausi_tausi-nyati-dudu-mende"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tausi"," userResponse":" tausi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775057619","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775057619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" punda_kobe-kuchakuro-punda-bata"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" punda"," userResponse":" punda"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775072021","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775072020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" kiboko_kiboko-duma-mbuni-paa"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kiboko"," userResponse":" kiboko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775081175","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775081175"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" kuchakuro_sungura-kuchakuro-buibui-swala"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuchakuro"," userResponse":" kuchakuro"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775095121","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775095121"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" kobe_chura-kobe-bata-nyani"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kobe"," userResponse":" kobe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775104979","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775104978"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tembo_tembo-duma-mende-punda"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" tembo"," userResponse":" duma"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775112575","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775112575"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" tembo_tembo-duma-mende-punda"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" tembo"," userResponse":" tembo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775125453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775125453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" paka_paka-kobe-mbuni-chura"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" paka"," userResponse":" paka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775136542","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775136542"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" vipepeo_sungura-buibui-vipepeo-nyati"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" vipepeo"," userResponse":" vipepeo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775146353","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775146353"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" mbuzi_paa-mbuzi-simba-sungura"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbuzi"," userResponse":" mbuzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775151892","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775151892"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" nyani_simba-nyati-nyani-farasi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nyani"," userResponse":" nyati"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775159797","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775159797"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" animals_1"," problemName":" nyani_simba-nyati-nyani-farasi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" nyani"," userResponse":" nyani"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"picmatch:animals","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775161773","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775161772"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" nyani_simba-nyati-nyani-farasi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775166540","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775166539"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nyani_simba-nyati-nyani-farasi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775175805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775175804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 1c945fa1-a817-4e42-8a8d-0135a5ac8cb8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" picmatch"," tutorId":" picmatch_animals"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" pm"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" nyani_simba-nyati-nyani-farasi"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775182402","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775182402"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" e01bb04e-9bca-4d1c-9280-c06dd0394406"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775182739","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775182738"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" e01bb04e-9bca-4d1c-9280-c06dd0394406"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775182785","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775182785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" e01bb04e-9bca-4d1c-9280-c06dd0394406"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775193022","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775193021"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kaka_dada-mwanafunzi-kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kaka"," userResponse":" kaka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775197593","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775197592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_babu_babu-mama-bibi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" babu"," userResponse":" babu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775202530","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775202530"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_baba_baba-dada-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" baba"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775211498","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775211498"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kinyozi_mkulima-kinyozi-bibi"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kinyozi"," userResponse":" kinyozi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775219815","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775219815"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwalimu_mjoma-mwalimu-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwalimu"," userResponse":" mwalimu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775227369","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775227369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mjoma_baba-kaka-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mjoma"," userResponse":" mjoma"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775232164","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775232164"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_dada-mkulima-mjoma"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dada"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775238405","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775238404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mwanafunzi_mwanafunzi-mama-shangazi"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mwanafunzi"," userResponse":" mwanafunzi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775243592","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775243592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bibi_mwanafunzi-dada-bibi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bibi"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775249602","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775249602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_bibi_mwanafunzi-dada-bibi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" bibi"," userResponse":" bibi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775254953","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775254953"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mkulima_babu-bibi-mkulima"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mkulima"," userResponse":" mkulima"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775260698","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775260697"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_mkulima_babu-bibi-mkulima"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775266220","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775266220"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 965c3ed7-b980-4a2d-b2c9-d503d2a571e0"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.show.5"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_mkulima_babu-bibi-mkulima"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775278143","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775278143"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 6505fd82-7011-4beb-bf87-1070cdc756d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_baba-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dada"," userResponse":" baba"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775283912","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775283912"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 6505fd82-7011-4beb-bf87-1070cdc756d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_baba-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dada"," userResponse":" dada"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775299557","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775299557"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 6505fd82-7011-4beb-bf87-1070cdc756d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_baba-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775306011","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775306010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 6505fd82-7011-4beb-bf87-1070cdc756d3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.people.lc.rand.stat.noShow.6"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_dada_baba-mjoma-dada"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775317411","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775317411"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775322017","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775322017"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775323571","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775323571"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775328677","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775328676"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775330222","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775330222"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775333612","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775333612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775335173","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775335173"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" MWANAFUNZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775339771","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775339771"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775341335","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775341335"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775345779","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775345779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775347340","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775347340"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775350586","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775350585"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775352150","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775352150"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775355708","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775355707"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775357259","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775357259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775360805","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775360805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775362364","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775362364"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMA"," userResponse":" MJOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775365925","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775365925"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775367480","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775367480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775370802","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775370802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775372357","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775372357"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775377332","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775377332"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775378894","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775378894"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775383018","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775383018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775385027","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775385027"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775385189","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775385189"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775390024","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775390023"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 4e55eff9-021f-4928-9b3b-6dca571ca9ce"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775400987","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775400987"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775402029","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775402029"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775405135","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775405135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775406175","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775406174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mjoma"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MJOMA"," userResponse":" MJOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775409501","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775409500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775410535","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775410535"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775413511","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775413511"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775413803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775413802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775414641","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775414640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775417363","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775417363"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" bibi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BIBI"," userResponse":" BIBI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775420508","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775420508"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775422137","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775422137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mkulima"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKULIMA"," userResponse":" MKULIMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775426077","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775426077"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775427221","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775427221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" START_MWANAFUNZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775427228","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775427228"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwanafunzi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANAFUNZI"," userResponse":" MWANAFUNZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775429423","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775429423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775430453","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775430453"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" shangazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775432690","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775432690"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775433720","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775433719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kinyozi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYOZI"," userResponse":" KINYOZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775437617","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775437617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775438649","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775438649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" babu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABU"," userResponse":" BABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775441750","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775441750"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775442790","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775442790"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" mwalimu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWALIMU"," userResponse":" MWALIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775446216","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775446215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775447260","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775447260"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775450837","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775450837"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775450991","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775450991"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" 45dbb0dd-6086-45fa-9fe1-00f49484ce22"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__comm_wrd.cat-people.rand.13"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775457621","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775457620"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" d79b66ce-8fa9-474e-9e38-559be0952bdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" START"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" tap"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775457909","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775457909"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" d79b66ce-8fa9-474e-9e38-559be0952bdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775457964","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775457964"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" d79b66ce-8fa9-474e-9e38-559be0952bdc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" 0"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" 10"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" ENDPROBLEM"," userResponse":" ENDPROBLEM"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" ENDPROBLEM"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775607543","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775607543"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" ea54c4ed-911f-4c09-9890-d83fbfcba5cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.wrd:lc.wrd.cat-people.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549775610047","data":{"timestamp":" 1549775610047"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190210_080055"," gameId":" ea54c4ed-911f-4c09-9890-d83fbfcba5cb"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.wrd_lc.wrd.cat-people.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_kaka"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}